Register of the Frances E. Willis Papers, 1906-1983.
Hoover Institution Archives
- AMBASSADOR TO NORWAY, 1957-1961
  - Chronological file of speeches and visits. Holograph notes, typewritten outline and text, correspondence.
    - Commendable Service Award Ceremony, February 1, 1961
    - Norwegian American Chamber of Commerce Meeting, February 6, 1961
    - The Norway America Association, February 21, 1961 and Kolsas (?) Wives Club, February 23, 1961
  - Subject file, 1957-1961. Correspondence, career records, memoranda, memorabilia, etc.
    - Accident of Ambassador Willis (Folder 11)
    - Bodo Lofoten Islands, trip to, March 16-19, 1957 (Folder 12)
    - Career records. Notes on GNP of Norway, personal notes relating to ambassadorial duties, diplomatic mission in Norway, etc. (Folder 13)
    - Department of State. Booklets, manuals, bulletins, procedures (Folder 14)
    - Department of State instructions (Folder 15)
    - Departure from Norway (Folder 16)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Folder 17)
    - Embassy Bulletin (Folder 18)
    - Embassy. Christmas gratuities (Folder 19)
    - Embassy organization (Folder 20)
    - Entertaining. Receipts, guest lists (Folder 21)
    - Foreign Service Extension Education Department. Continuing education, self-assessed language proficiency (Folder 22)
    - Menus, invitations, programs, namecards (Folder 23)
    - Memoranda (Box 22.)
      - Undated (Folder 1)
      - 1957 (Folder 2)
      - 1958 (Folder 3)
      - 1959 (Folder 4)
      - 1960 (Folder 5)
      - 1961 (Folder 6)
    - Miscellany (Folder 7)
    - Norway
      - Defense (Folder 8)
      - Foreign Ministers Statement, March 9, 1961 (Folder 9)
    - Personal business and household employees (Folder 10)
    - Presentation of medal by the President of the U.S.A. honoring Norwegian Air Force Pilot Fenrik Arne Vatne (Folder 11)
    - Press releases and USIA Information Releases (Folder 12)
    - Security violations (Folder 13)
    - Souvenir booklets (Folder 14)
    - Travel vouchers and itinerary (Folder 15)
    - United Nations (Folder 16)
    - Visitors (Folder 17)
  - Clippings, 1957-1961 (Box 23.)
    - 1957 (Folder 1-3)
    - 1958 (Folder 4-5)
    - 1959 (Folder 6-7)
    - 1960 (Folder 8)
    - 1961 (Folder 9)
- AMBASSADOR TO SRI LANKA, 1961-1964
  - Correspondence (Box 24.)
    - Undated (Folder 1)
    - Collected (Folder 2)
    - 1961 (Folder 3)
    - 1962 (Folder 4-5)
    - 1963 (Folder 6)
    - 1964 (Folder 7-9)
  - Chronological file of speeches and visits. Holograph notes, typewritten outline and text, correspondence.
  - Fragments and holograph notes, etc. (Folder 9a)
  - "Political Power in Ceylon," n.d. (Folder 9b)
    - "The Power of Choice," n.d.
    - "Disarmament," n.d.
    - "United States Foreign Policy," YWCA and Ceylon American Society, Kandy, n.d.
    - American Association of Colombo, June 6, 1961 (Folder 10)
    - Remarks on American Foreign Policy, June 7, 1961 (Folder 11)
    - American Association Celebration of the Fourth of July, Colombo, July 4, 1961 (Folder 12)
    - Opening of Cancer Week, Ceylon Cancer Society, July 8, 1961 (Folder 13)
    - YMCA of Colombo, July 11, 1961, and Midland Ceylon American Society, July 12, 1961 (Folder 14)
    - Kingswood College, Kandy, July 15, 1961 (Folder 15)
    - Dutch Reformed Sunday Schools, Wolrendaal Church, July 24, 1961 (Folder 16)
    - Opening of the Housewives' Exhibition, Colombo Art Gallery, July 28, 1961 (Folder 17)
    - Opening Ceremony of the Stanford Management Seminar, Ceylon, July 31, 1961 (Folder 18)
    - Pageant of Flowers, Church of Ceylon Sunday Schools, August 13, 1961 (Folder 19)
    - Remarks made to Embassy wives, October 5, 1961 (Folder 20)
    - Association of Teachers of Domestic Science, St. Bridget's Convent, October 7, 1961 (Folder 21)
    - St. Benedict's College, October 8, 1961 (Folder 22)
    - "What Everyone Serving the United States Government Aboard Should Know," USOM Orientation Program, October 14, 1961 (Folder 23)
    - "Maternity and Child Welfare," League of Wellewalte, October 14, 1961 (Folder 24)
    - Western Province Girls' Schools, Athletic Association Championship Meet, October 20, 1961 (Folder 25)
    - "American Foreign Policy," Vincent Girls' High School, Batticaloa, October 27, 1961 (Folder 26)
    - USOM Award of Certification of Achievement, Red Cross Hall, November 14, 1961 (Folder 27)
    - YMCA Christmas Dinner, December 20, 1961 (Folder 28)
    - Dedication of the Building Given to the YMCA by the American Women's Club of Colombo, January 23, 1962 (Box 25.1)
    - "Some Aspects of American Foreign Policy," Colombo Rotary Club, February 15, 1962 (Folder 2)
    - Bishop's School, February 16, 1962 (Folder 3)
    - "Role of University Women in Public Life," Seminar of the Ceylon Federation of University Women, Radus (?) College, February 17, 1962 (Folder 4)
    - "Some Aspects of American Foreign Policy," Women's International Club, February 20, 1962 (Folder 5)
    - Commemoration of the Fiftieth Anniversary of the Death of the Venerable Sri Sumangala Nayaka Thero, Vidyodaya University, April 28, 1962 (Folder 6)
    - Reception for Returned Grantees, Ministry of Transport and Communications, USAid Mission, May 10, 1962 (Folder 7)
    - Opening of the Exhibition of American Arts and Crafts, Kandy, June 7, 1962 (Folder 8)
    - Jaffna College, June 9, 1962 (Folder 9)
    - Opening of the Exhibition of Friendship, Lt. Col. John Glenn's Spaceship, National Museum, Colombo, June 28, 1962 (Folder 10)
    - American Picnic, Race Course, July 4, 1962 (Folder 11)
    - Remarks for Broadcast by Radio Ceylon, July 4, 1962 (Folder 12)
    - "A Message on the National Holiday of the United States of America from the American Ambassador," July 4, 1962 (Folder 13)
    - Remarks on sports, August 5, 1962 (Folder 14)
    - Prize Day of the Trinity College of Music, Ladies College, Colombo, August 11, 1962 (Folder 15)
    - Annual Dinner of the Ceylon Association of Pediatricians, August 11, 1962 (Folder 16)
    - Opening of the Sarana Feteana Fair (Uelala), September 1, 1962 (Folder 17)
    - Welcome Address to Peace Corps Volunteers, September 8, 1962 (Folder 18)
    - Award Presentation to the US Marine Corps, Certificate of Good Conduct, presented to Corporal Daniel Naclaw, September 11, 1962 (Folder 19)
    - Ceylon American Youth League, Matura, September 19, 1962 (Folder 20)
    - Opening of the Central Vocational Training and Trade Testing Centre, October 5, 1962 (Folder 21)
    - Salvation Army Girl's Home, Dehiwela, November 24, 1962 (Folder 22)
    - American Women's Club, Tenth Anniversary, December 15, 1962 (Folder 23)
    - Opening of the Jaffna YMCA, Jaffna, December 29, 1962 (Folder 24)
    - Silaboli Exhibition and Fair, March 9, 1963 (Folder 25)
    - Bible Society Sale, June 1, 1963 (Folder 26)
    - CARE Presentation of Eleven Sets of Bottling Equipment to Lanka Mahila Samita(?), June 1, 1963 (Folder 27)
    - Annual General Meeting of the CNAPT, June 28, 1963 (Folder 28)
    - American Picnic, Cricket Club, July 4, 1963 (Folder 29)
    - "United States Participation in International Organizations and Activities," Rotary Club, Colombo West, August 21, 1963 (Folder 30)
    - "United States Participation in International Organizations," Mt. Lavinia Rotary Club, August 27, 1963 (Folder 31)
    - Exhibition of Paintings and Drawing of Patricia Jeffrey, Lionel Munde Memorial Hall, September 6, 1963 (Folder 32)
    - Safety Seminar, Colombo Oval, November 1, 1963 (Folder 33)
    - Opening Ceremony of the Alutnuwara-Padiyatalawa, January 30, 1964 (Folder 34)
    - AWA Annual Meeting and Luncheon, March 3, 1964 (Folder 35)
    - World Health Day Celebration, Colombo, April 7, 1964 (Folder 36)
    - School for the Blind, Mt. Lavinia, April 9, 1964 (Folder 37)
    - Church of Ceylon, Board of Women's Work, May Time Fair, YMCA Jubilee Hall, May 9, 1964 (Folder 38)
    - Luncheon held in honor of F. E. Willis' 65th Birthday, May 20, 1964 (Folder 39)
    - All Ceylon Government English Assistant Teachers' Trade Union, Ganipahe, June 13, 1964 (Folder 40)
    - American Celebration, July 5, 1964 (Folder 41)
    - St. Michael's Youth Group, August 13, 1964 (Folder 42)
    - Statement of Ambassador upon Departure from Ceylon, 1964 (Folder 43)
  - Subject file, 1961-1964. Correspondence, memoranda, career records, printed matter, bulletins, etc. (Box 26.)
    - Ambassador's appointments (Folder 1)
    - American citizens in Ceylon (Folder 2)
    - American Community Center (Folder 3)
    - Appointment to Ceylon (Folder 4)
    - Atomic Energy Test Ban Treaty, 1963 (Folder 5)
    - Belgian-American Education Foundation (Folder 6)
    - Career records. Promotion, leave, shipment of effects, biographic data sheet, appointment affidavits, allotment of pay, travel voucher (Folder 7)
    - Ceylon. U.S. Aid (Folder 8)
    - Colombo Plan. Cooperative Economic Development of South and Southeast Asia (Folder 9)
    - Department of State (Folder 10)
    - Education. Ryan, Bruce, "The Dilemmas of Education in Ceylon." (Folder 11)
    - Embassy
      - Duty officers conduct (Folder 12)
      - Gratuities (Folder 13)
      - Information bulletins (Folder 14)
      - Personnel (Folder 15)
    - Fourth of July (Box 27.)
      - 1961 (Folder 1)
      - 1962 (Folder 2)
      - 1963 (Folder 3)
      - 1964 (Folder 4)
    - Grant, Robert Y. (Folder 5)
    - International Cooperation Administration (Folder 6)
    - Iran (Folder 6a)
    - Kennedy, President John F.
      - Correspondence (Folder 7)
      - Death (Folder 8)
      - Printed matter (Folder 9)
    - Map of Colombo (Box 28.1)
    - Memoranda, 1961-1964 (Folder 2)
    - Miscellany (Folder 3)
    - National Civil Service League Award to Frances Willis (Folder 4)
    - Newsbriefs, digests, bulletins
      - Undated (Folder 5)
      - 1961
        - March (Folder 6)
        - June (Folder 7)
        - July (Folder 8)
        - August (Folder 9)
        - September (Folder 10)
        - October-December (Folder 11)
      - 1962
        - January-March (Folder 12)
        - April-June (Folder 13)
        - July-September (Folder 14)
        - October-December (Folder 15)
      - 1963
        - January-February (Folder 16)
        - May (Box 29.1)
        - June (Folder 2)
        - July-September, December (Folder 3)
      - 1964
        - January-February (Folder 4)
        - April-August (Folder 5)
    - Norge-Amerika Foreningen (Folder 6)
    - Nuclear Energy Test Ban Treaty (Folder 7)
    - Organization of American States (Folder 8)
    - Printed material (Folder 9)
    - Rusk, Dean (Folder 10)
    - Society for the Cause of Mother's Lineage (Folder 11)
    - Southeast Asia, proposed economic conference (Folder 12)
    - Souvenir, proclamation (Folder 13)
    - Sri Lanka
      - Ambassador to the United States (Folder 14)
      - Economic conditions (Folder 15)
      - Rainfall (Folder 16)
    - Tamil. Karalasingham, V., "The Way Out for the Tamil- Speaking People." (Folder 17)
    - Thanksgiving (Folder 18)
    - Travel
      - England (Folder 19)
      - India, Nepal, Pakistan, Iran (Folder 20)
      - Japan (Folder 21)
      - Sri Lanka
        - General (Folder 22)
        - Alutnuwara Rd. (Folder 23)
        - Ampara (Folder 24)
        - Galle (Folder 25)
        - Kandy (Folder 26)
        - Matara and Hambantota (Folder 27)
      - Washington, D.C. (Folder 28)
    - Trinity College of Music (Ceylon Center) (Box 30.1)
    - United Nations (Folder 2)
    - United States
      - Ambassador to Vietnam (Folder 3)
      - Foreign aid (Folder 4)
      - Policy towards Communist China (Folder 5)
    - U.S.S.R. "The Sources of Soviet Conduct," by X (George Kennan), with clipping by Walter Lippmann (Folder 6)
    - Visit of Mrs. de Marconnay (Folder 7)
    - Voice of America (Folder 8)
    - Women's International Club (Folder 9)
    - Y.M.C.A., Jaffna (Folder 10)
  - Clippings
    - 1961 (Folder 11)
    - 1962 (Box 31.1-2)
    - 1963 (Folder 3)
    - 1964 (Folder 4-6)
- POST-RETIREMENT, 1964-1983
  - Correspondence (Box 32.)
    - 1964 (Folder 1-2)
    - 1965 (Folder 3)
    - 1966 (Folder 4)
    - 1967 (Folder 5)
    - 1968 (Folder 6)
    - 1969 (Folder 7)
    - 1970 (Folder 8)
    - 1971 (Folder 9)
    - 1972 (Folder 10)
    - 1973 (Folder 11)
    - 1977 (Folder 12)
    - 1978 (Folder 13)
  - Chronological file of speeches and visits. Holograph notes, typewritten outline and text, correspondence. (Box 33.)
    - Introduction of Dr. Frances Elizabeth Willis, 1965 (Folder 1)
    - Mount Senior Convocation of Western College for Women, Oxford, Ohio, February 13, 1965 (Folder 2)
    - Redlands Reading Club, March 4, 1965 (Folder 3)
    - P.E.O. Sisterhood, Redlands, March 15, 1965 (Folder 4)
    - Joint meeting of the Rotary Club of Redlands and the Soroptimist Club, March 25, 1965 (Folder 5)
    - Young People's Fellowship, Trinity Episcopal Church, Redlands, April 4, 1965 (Folder 6)
    - Yucaipa Rotary Club, April 6, 1965 (Folder 7)
    - Riverside Rotary Club, May 12, 1965 (Folder 8)
    - "Afterthoughts of an Ambassador," Kiwanis Club, Riverside, August 26, 1965 (Folder 9)
    - Citrus Belt, U.N.A., Ramada Inn, Riverside, January 8, 1966 (Folder 10)
    - "The United Nations General Assembly," Retired Officers Club, Norton Air Force Base, January 28, 1966 (Folder 11)
    - United Nations Association, Long Beach, January 29, 1966 (Folder 12)
    - "The United Nations - The General Assembly," Business and Professional Women, San Bernardino, February 1, 1966 (Folder 13)
    - Breakfast Club, Redlands, February 3, 1966 (Folder 14)
    - "What a Foreign Service Officer is Expected to Do," Junior Contemporary Club, March 5, 1966 (Folder 15)
    - American Association of Retired Persons, Redlands Branch, April 18, 1966 (Folder 16)
    - Contemporary Club, April 18, 1966 (Folder 17)
    - U.N.A., Palm Springs, April 25, 1966 (Folder 18)
    - "Look Who is Doing the Talking," Kemper Hall, May 7, 1966 (Folder 19)
    - Redlands Lions Club, May 27, 1966 (Folder 20)
    - Red Cross Annual Award Ceremony, Redlands, June 15, 1966 (Folder 21)
    - China Lake Chapter of the American Society for Public Administration, December 6, 1966 (Folder 22)
    - "The Christian's Mission in a World of Dilemma," Congregation Church, Redlands Christian Fellowship Meeting, January 4, 1967 (Folder 23)
    - "The United States in a Changing World," The Clark Lecture, Scripps College, Claremont, January 10, 1967. Printed program of speech, programs, clippings, menu and seating charts, schedules (Folder 24)
    - "The U.S. Foreign Service and the Role of an Ambassador," Lawyer's Wives Annual Benefit Luncheon, San Bernardino, February 8, 1967 (Folder 25)
    - "Christianity in a Changing World," El Centro, February 14, 1967 (Folder 26)
    - American Association of University Women, Redlands March 7, 1967 (Box 34.1)
    - "Your Representatives Abroad," Torch Club, San Bernardino, May 10, 1967 (Folder 2)
    - "Our Changing World," Cap and Gown, Stanford, May 13, 1967 (Folder 3)
    - Knights of the Round Table, Grail Award, Acceptance Speech, Redlands, June 27, 1967 (Folder 4)
    - Presentation of Red Cross Length of Service Award, September 18, 1967 (Folder 5)
    - "The Foreign Service of the United States, Your Representative Abroad," Nine O'Clock Players, Hollywood, October 4, 1967 (Folder 6)
    - "The United States in a Changing World," Fortnightly Club, October 7, 1967 (Folder 7)
    - "The Need to Know," Sweet Briar College, Founder's Day Address, October 18, 1967 (Folder 8)
    - Introduction of the Honorable William P. Bundy, World Affairs Council Inland Southern California, San Bernardino Orange Show, October 11, 1967 (Folder 9)
    - Prospect Park Volunteer Meeting, Casa Loma, University of Redlands (?), November 6, 1967 (Folder 10)
    - California League of Senior Citizens, January 3, 1968 (Folder 11)
    - Introduction of Fulton Freeman, U.S. Ambassador to Mexico, Redlands Community Forum, January 24, 1968 (Folder 12)
    - Highland Women's Club, February 9, 1968 (Folder 13)
    - Book Club, Redlands, March 7 1968 (Folder 14)
    - "The Role of the United States in a Changing World," Loma Linda, March 18, 1968 (Folder 15)
    - "The U.S. Foreign Service and the Role of an Ambassador," Banning Women's Club, March 26, 1968 (Folder 16)
    - University of Redlands, March 28, 1968 (Folder 17)
    - "The Role of Women in the Observance of International Human Rights Year," Yokohoma, Japan, May 14, 1968 (Folder 18)
    - Tsuda College, May 16, 1968 (Folder 19)
    - "Human Rights, Avenue to Progress," Women Leaders, Tokyo, May 17, 1968 (Folder 20)
    - "The Role of Women in Good Government," Hiroshima, May 21, 1968 (Folder 21)
    - Japanese American Society, Osaka, May 30, 1968 (Folder 22)
    - Fourth Conference of the Status of Women Commission, June 22, 1968 (Folder 23)
    - "The Foreign Service," Redlands High School, July 8, 1968 (Folder 24)
    - Baptist Women's Society of the First Baptist Church in Redlands, September 11, 1968 (Folder 25)
    - "The United Nations," Kiwanis Club, Redlands, November 26, 1968 (Folder 26)
    - IX Foreign Service Day Program, Acceptance Speech, U.S. Department of State, November 16, 1973 (Folder 27)
    - Unidentified speech 1974 (Folder 28)
    - "Abraham Lincoln: His Views Applied Today," Watchorn Lincoln Dinner, Redlands Round Table International, February 12, 1974 (Folder 29)
    - Model U.N. Conference, VII, February 22, 1974 (Folder 30)
    - International Club of the California State College, San Bernardino, April 13, 1974 (Folder 31)
    - California Baptist College, Riverside, April 26, 1974 (Folder 32)
    - Board of Overseers, University of Redlands, June 2, 1974 (Folder 33)
    - United Nations Association, San Bernardino, October 25, 1974 (Folder 34)
    - Book Club, October 3, 1974 (Folder 35)
    - Unidentified speech, November 1974 (Folder 36)
    - United Nations Association Dinner, October 22, 1975 (Folder 37)
    - "Round the World Journey," Book Club, November 6, 1975 (Folder 38)
    - Round Table, Luncheon Meeting, December 2, 1975 (Folder 39)
  - Subject file, 1964-1983. Correspondence, memorabilia, printed matter, etc. (Box 35.)
    - American Foreign Service Association (Folder 1)
    - American Red Cross (Folder 2)
    - American-Scandinavian Foundation (Folder 3)
    - American Society for Friendship with Switzerland (Folder 4)
    - American-Swiss Association (Folder 5)
    - American Women's Association (Folder 6)
    - Council of Community Service (Folder 7)
    - Crowe, Philip K., writings (Folder 8)
    - Department of State
      - General (Folder 9)
      - Publication, "Women in American Foreign Affairs" (Folder 10)
      - Stimulation of Creativity Task Force (Folder 11)
    - Economic Commission for Europe (Box 36.1)
    - Europe, travel in, 1966 (Folder 2)
    - Foreign Policy Conference (Folder 3)
    - Foreign Service Journal (Folder 4)
    - Hollins College (Folder 5)
    - Japan, travel in, 1968 (Folder 6-7)
    - Miscellany (Box 37.1)
    - Pitzer College (Folder 2)
    - Redlands, California Chamber of Commerce (Folder 3)
    - Sri Lanka (Folder 4)
    - Swiss Society of New York (Folder 5)
    - United Nations (Folder 6)
    - University of California, Riverside (Folder 7)
    - Vietnam (Folder 8)
    - Western College for Women, Oxford, Ohio (Folder 9)
    - Women (Folder 10)
  - Clippings (Box 38.)
    - Undated (Folder 1)
    - 1964 (Folder 2)
    - 1965 (Folder 3)
    - 1966 (Folder 4)
    - 1967 (Folder 5)
    - 1968 (Folder 6)
    - 1969 (Folder 7)
    - 1970 (Folder 8)
    - 1971 (Folder 9)
    - 1972 (Folder 10)
    - 1973 (Folder 11)
    - 1974 (Folder 12)
    - 1975 (Folder 13)
    - 1976 (Folder 14)
- OVERSIZE.
  - One box containing identity cards, passports, membership cards, certificates, awards, appointment book (1977), book of Swiss stamps, dinner record book (1957), guest book, diplomas and honorary degrees, retirement certificate, commemorative stamp booklet, and other memorabilia. (Box 39.)
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1916-1979.
  - Album of prints in Belgium, 1939; 4 albums of Switzerland, 1953-1957. (Folder fA)
  - 1 album in Switzerland, 1954; 3 albums in Norway, 1957-1961 (Folder fB)
  - 3 albums in Sri Lanka., 1961-1964 (Folder fC)
  - 4 prints of Frances Willis at Stanford graduation, 1923; 3 prints of Frances Willis and others in Chile; 5 prints of scenes in Peru. (Folder D)
  - 3 prints of Francis Willis; 2 prints of Francis Willis and others., circa 1930 (Folder mE)
  - 3 prints of Frances Willis, Chile; 11 prints of Francis Willis and others, Chile, 1928-1931; 1 print of Stanford University, 1928. (Folder F)
  - 4 prints of Frances Willis' living quarters, Stockholm; 5 outdoor scenes; 5 prints of Francis Willis; 1 print of unidentified man; 24 prints of Frances Willis and others; 2 unidentified prints; 2 prints of Julius Wadsworth; 1931-1934; 13 prints of Frances Willis, American Ambassador and Mrs. Moorehead (?) and others, 1933; 1 print of Agnes and William Dawson; 1 print of Frances Willis and Anne Morrow Lindbergh; 2 prints of Charles and Anne Lindbergh, leaving Stockholm; 1 print of Charles and Anne Lindbergh and others; 1 print of Charles Lindbergh and others, 1933. (Folder G)
  - 3 prints of Captain C.H.J Keppler, U.S. Navy; 3 prints of Frances Willis; 17 prints of Francis Willis and others; 23 unidentified prints; 1 outdoor scene; 2 prints of indoor scenes; 1 print of King Leopold of Belgium; 1 print of Queen Astrid of Belgium, 1934-1940. (Folder H)
  - 5 prints of Frances Willis and others in Spain, circa 1941; 5 unidentified prints in Spain; 1 print of Frances Willis and others, 1948; 3 prints of Francis Willis, Joseph C. Grew and others; 1 unidentified print; 1 print of wedding, 1950; 1 print of Frances Willis and others, 1950; 1 print of Frances Willis, 1951. (Folder I)
  - 14 prints of Frances Willis and others, circa 1952; 4 prints of Frances Willis, circa 1952, Helsinki, Finland; 4 scenes of Finland; 1 print of the American Legation, Helsinki, Finland. (Folder J)
  - 2 prints of Frances Willis., circa 1952 (Folder mK)
  - 10 prints of scenes in Switzerland,; 3 unidentified prints., circa 1953 (Folder L)
  - 8 prints of Frances Willis in Switzerland; 78 prints of Frances Willis and others during her Ambassadorship., 1953-1957 (Folder M)
  - 21 prints of Frances Willis and others; 2 prints of Francis Willis., 1953 (Folder N)
  - 4 prints of Frances Willis, Mr. and Mrs. John Foster Dulles, and others, 1954; 33 prints of Frances Willis and others; 17 prints of Frances Willis and others at "Hospes" Exhibition, Bern, Switzerland, given by U.S. Lines, June, 1954. (Folder O)
  - 10 prints of Frances Willis, President and Mrs. Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1955; 6 prints of Frances Willis, 1955; 23 prints of Frances Willis and others; 16 prints of Frances Willis and family members, circa 1955; 2 prints of Frances Willis and her mother at a concert, June 1955 (Folder P)
  - 1 print of Frances Willis, President and Mrs. Dwight D. Eisenhower, and others, July 1955; 3 prints of the American Embassy in Switzerland, 3 sets of Album pages of Frances Willis and others, 1955, 1956, 1957. (Folder mQ)
  - 11 prints of the American Embassy, Oslo, Norway; 6 prints of the U.S.S. Intrepid; 4 prints of Frances Willis and others aboard the U.S.S. Intrepid, 1958; 3 prints of Frances Willis and others, 1959. (Folder mR)
  - 1 print of Frances Willis in Switzerland; 67 prints of Frances Willis and others, Switzerland., 1956 (Folder S)
  - 1 print of Frances Willis and under Secretary Robert Murphy; 1 print of Frances Willis and John Foster Dulles. 1 print of Frances Willis, John Foster Dulles and others; 12 prints of Frances Willis and others., 1957 (Folder T)
  - 7 prints of Frances Willis and others, Norway; 9 prints of Frances Willis and others at a ship launching, Norway; 4 unidentified prints (Folder U)